Sacks, Robert L. Collection of National Handbag Association Agreements and Arbitration Decisions 6403
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert L. Sacks Collection of National Handbag Association Agreements and Arbitration Decisions
1918-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sacks, Robert L.
6403
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Agreements, arbitration decisions, records.
8889599
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 11, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective labor agreements; Sacks, Robert L.; National Handbag Association
8889599
- Leather Goods Manufacturer's Association Agreements, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Leather Goods Manufacturers Agreements, 1920-1926 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Leather Goods Manufacturers Agreements, 1931-1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- New York Handbag Manufactures Agreement, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Nat'l. Authority for Ladies' Handbag Industry Agreements, 1944-1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Nat'l. Authority for Ladies' Handbag Industry Agreements, 1951-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Harlic Bag Company Agreements, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Nat'l. Authority for Ladies' Handbag Industry Agreements, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- H. Margolin and Company Agreements, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- National Handbag Association Agreements, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- National Handbag Association Agreements, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- National Handbag Association and Joint Board Agreements, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- National Handbag Association Agreements, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- National Handbag Association and Joint Board Agreement, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- National Handbag Association and Local 1 Agreements, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- National Handbag Association Cost of Living Adjustment, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- National Handbag Association and Joint Board Agreement, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- National Handbag Association and Local 1 Agreement, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- National Handbag Association and Joint Board Agreement, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- National Handbag Association and Local 1 Agreement, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- National Handbag Association and Local 1 Agreement, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- National Handbag Association Agreements, 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Morris White Fashion Agreements (Published), 1962-1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- National Handbag Association Agreements (Published), 1965-1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- National Handbag Association Agreements (Published), 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- National Fashion Accessories Association and Joint Boards Agreements, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- National Fashion Accessories Association and Local 1 Agreements, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- National Fashion Accessories Association and Joint Board Agreement, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- National Fashion Accessories Association and Local 1 Agreement, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- National Fashion Accessories Association and Local 1 Memorandum of Understanding, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- National Fashion Accessories Association and Local 1 Agreement, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Local 1 Correspondences, 1978-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- National Fashion Accessories' Association and Local 1 Agreements, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- National Fashion Accessories Association and Local 1 Memorandum of Agreement, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Corrected Agreement Pages, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- National Fashion Accessories Association and Local 1 Agreement, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Arbitration, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Arbitration, 1971-1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Arbitration, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Arbitration, 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Arbitration, 1987-1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1967-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)